A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices, Paris, RG 6, SG 1 FA395
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Post-war, 1945-1959; 2; 81 Boxes; 42 cubic feet
  - Post-war - Correspondence, 01
    - NSA Yugoslavia, 1950-1955 (Box 9, Folder 68)
      Bogdanovitch, Jinisha - (fellowship, physiology) - 1951-1953 Borojevic, Slavko - (fellowship, plant breeding) - 1950-1952 Milinkovic, Vinko - (fellowship, plant breeding) - 1952 Terminated grants - (actions and copies only) - 1951-1952 Thaller, Viktor - (fellowship, biochemistry) - 1951-1955
    - NSA Yugoslavia, 1947-1955 (Box 9, Folder 69)
      Norwegian Radium Hospital - 1950-1955 Oslo University - (miscellaneous) - 1947-1955 Terminated grants - (actions and copies only) - 1948-1954
    - NSA Poland - Fellowship List, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - NSA Scotland, 1947-1956 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      Edinburgh University - Medical Chemistry - 1951-1955 Glasgow University - Biochemistry - 1947-1952 Terminated grants - (actions and copies only) - 1950-1956
    - NSA Sweden - Goteborg University - Institute of Histology, 1949-1954 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - NSA Sweden, 1946-1956 (Box 9, Folder 73)
      Karolinska Institute - Anatomy - 1947-1954 Karolinska Institute - Biochemistry - 1947-1955 Karolinska Institute - Chemical Institute - 1946-1955 Karolinska Institute - Physical Cell Research - 1947-1954 Sorbo, Bo Hilding - (fellowship, biochemistry) - 1954-1956 Uppsala University - Physiology - 1947-1955 Uppsala University - Biochemistry - 1949-1953
    - NSA Sweden - Terminated grants - (actions and copies only), 1946-1957 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - NSA Switzerland, 1946-1955 (Box 10, Folder 75)
      Bern University - Kocher Institute - (experimental biology) - 1950-1955 Geneva University - Chemistry - 1948-1953 Geneva University - Institute of Zoology - 1951-1954 Horber, Ernst - (travel, entomology) - 1951-1952 Terminated grants - (miscellaneous actions and correspondence) - 1947-1954 Zurich Federal Technical High School - (organic chemistry) - 1946-1955
    - NSA United States, 1947-1954 (Box 10, Folder 76)
      Oster, Gerald - (fellowship, biology) - 1948-1951 Rowen, John W. - (travel, physiological chemistry) - 1953 Stern, Curt - (fellowship, genetics) - 1950-1952 Terminated grants - (miscellaneous actions and correspondence) - 1947-1954
    - IHD Denmark, 1946-1952 (Box 10, Folder 77)
      Bagger, Else Lykke - (fellowship, nursing) - 1948-1951 Broe, Ellen - (fellowship, nursing, TG) - 1946-1951 Dreyer, Karen - (fellowship, biostatistics) - 1951-1952
    - IHD England, 1947-1952 (Box 10, Folder 78)
      Isaacs, Peter Charles Gerard - (fellowships, public health engineering) - 1951-1952 London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - 1947
    - IHD England - Oxford Nutrition Survey, 1942-1945 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - IHD Finland - Heikinheimo, Aila Tellervo - (fellowship, nursing), 1948-1952 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - IHD Finland, 1946-1953 (Box 11, Folder 81)
      Huhtinen, Anna Sofia - (fellowship, maternal hygiene) - 1948-1953 Jaaskelainen, Timo - (fellowship, public health) - 1950-1951 Manni, Helen Mirsam Tuulikki - (fellowship, nursing) - 1950-1952 Peltonen, Hilkka - (fellowship, nursing) - 1949-1953 Public Health - 1946-1950
    - IHD France - Corsica Malaria Control, 1947-1954 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - IHD France - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 83)
      Cente de Recherches de l'Hygiene Foch Chevallier, Dr. Morin, G.S. Trefouel, Jacques Tremolieres, Dr. Trinquier, E.
    - IHD Germany, 1948-1953 (Box 11, Folder 84)
      Bretschneider, Johannes - (medical apparatus) - 1948 Leuchter, Heinrich - (fellowship, public health administration) - 1949-1953
    - IHD Germany - Sonntag, Susanne Elizabeth - (fellowship, nursing), 1949-1952 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - IHD Germany - Urban, Hans Joachim - (fellowship, public health education), 1951-1952 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - IHD Holland, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 87)
      Malaria Control - 1947-1948 Netherlands Applied Research Council - 1948 Public Health - 1947-1948
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zagreb School of Engineering, 1949-1955 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - IHD Yugoslavia - Zagreb School of Nursing, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - IHD Norway, 1948-1953 (Box 12, Folder 90)
      Aartun, Einar - (fellowship, public health) - 1948-1953 Bratlie, Solveig - (fellowship, nursing) - 1949-1951 Barlindhaug, Randi - (fellowship, nursing) - 1950-1952
    - IHD Norway, 1945-1952 (Box 12, Folder 91)
      Gudim, Berljlot - (fellowship, nursing) - 1948-1951 Larsen, Svenn - (fellowship, occupational hygiene) - 1949-1952 Oslo State Institute of Public Health - 1945, 1948 Oslo Statistical Department - 1946-1947 Stolen, Gunnar - (fellowship, industrial hygiene) - 1949-1951
    - IHD Poland, 1945-1948 (Box 12, Folder 92)
      Cracow School of Nursing - 1947-1948 Lazowski, Eugeniusz - (fellowship, public health) - 1947 Rockefeller Foundation - (former fellows) - 1946 Warsaw School of Hygiene - 1945-1947
    - IHD Portugal - Leite-Riberio, Maria Ofelia da Veiga - (fellowship, nursing), 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - IHD South Africa - Kark, Sydney L. - (travel, public health administration), 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - IHD Sweden - A 11 Scandinavian School of Public Health, 1950-1954 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - IHD Sweden, 1949-1953 (Box 12, Folder 96)
      Larsson, Alf Harald - (fellowship, occupational hygiene) - 1949-1952 Liljekrantz, Ulla B. - (fellowship, nursing) - 1949-1953
    - IHD Sweden - Lundgren, Ann-Margaret - "The Organization of Outpatient Care in Sweden", 1949 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - IHD Sweden - Sjobring, Marta Anna-Stina - (fellowship, nursing), 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - IHD Switzerland, 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 99)
      Grandjean, Etienne - (fellowship, industrial hygiene) - 1948-1951 Hogger, Dietrich - (fellowship, industrial medicine) - 1949-1951
    - IHD Switzerland - Langer, Denyse - (fellowship, nursing), 1949-1953 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - IHD Thailand - Binbakya, Chanmong - (nursing), 1950 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - IHD General, 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - IHD General - European Program - "Resumes of the Work of the International Health Division), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - DMPH Personnel - Boyd, Mark F., 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - DMPH Personnel - Brackett, Elizabeth W., 1952-1954 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - DMPH Personnel - Grant, John B., 1951-1954 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - DMPH Personnel - Leach, Charles N., 1945 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - DMPH Personnel - Logan, John A., 1951-1955 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - DMPH Personnel - Peterson, Osler L., 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - DMPH Personnel - Russell, Paul F., 1952-1955 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - DMPH Personnel - Struthers, Rolf R., 1948 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - DMPH Personnel - Tennant, Mary Elizabeth (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - DMPH Personnel - Watson, Robert Briggs, 1949-1953 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - DMPH Australia, 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 114)
      Rickards, Winston S. - (fellowship, psychiatry) - 1951-1953 Turner, Brian B. - (fellowship, neuropathology) - 1952-1955
    - DMPH Australia - Miscellaneous, 1948-1955 (Box 14, Folder 115)
      Granat, Malla - (declination, children's home) - 1951-1953 Holub, Karl - (neurosurgery) - 1952 Marberger, Hans - (urology) - 1955 Toman, Walter - (clinical psychology) - 1948-1954
    - DMPH Austria - Graz University - (Faculty of Medicine), 1948-1957 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - DMPH Austria - Graz University - Pharmacological Institute, 1949, 1952-1955 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - DMPH Austria - Graz University - Zoological Institute, 1951-1957 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - DMPH Austria - Innsbruck University - Institute of Pharmacology, 1947-1954 (Box 14, Folder 119)
    - DMPH Austria - Klimt, Christian R. - (fellowship, public health), 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    - DMPH Austria - Nursing, 1946-1953 (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - DMPH Austria - Rosenaur, Adolf - (fellowship, neurosurgery), 1949-1955 (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - DMPH Austria - Simandl, Edith - (fellowship, anesthesiology), 1948-1956 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - DMPH Austria - Vienna University, 1947-1954 (Box 14, Folder 124)
      Faculty of Medicine - 1947-1952 Institute of Pharmacology - 1948-1954
    - DMPH Austria - Vienna University - Psychiatric Clinic, 1947-1957 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - DMPH Belgium, 1951-1956 (Box 15, Folder 126)
      Bigwood, E.J. - (biochemistry and nutrition) - 1951-1956 Brussels University - (Faculty of Medicine) - 1951-1956
    - DMPH Belgium - Brussels University - Institut Jules Bordet - (cancer research), 1947-1955 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - DMPH Belgium - Brussels University - Institute of Social Medicine and Hygiene - (Graftar, Marcel), 1951-1957 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - DMPH Belgium - Brussels University - Neurophysiology - (Bremer, Frederic), 1939-1940, 1945-1957 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - DMPH Belgium - Brussels University - School of Nursing, 1946-1955 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - DMPH Belgium - Dalem, Jacques - (fellowship, cardiac surgery), 1950-1953 (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - DMPH Belgium, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 132)
      Declinations - 1954-1955 Institut Edith Cavell-Marie Depage - (nursing) - 1954
    - DMPH Belgium - Liege University - (Faculty of Medicine), 1947-1956 (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - DMPH Belgium, 1947-1955 (Box 16, Folder 134)
      Liege University - Laboratory of Neuroanatomy - 1947-1955 Reprints (17) - (Gerebtzoff, M.A.) - 1951-1953
    - DMPH Belgium, 1947-1955 (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - DMPH Belgium, 1948-1957 (Box 16, Folder 136)
      de Scoville, Albert - (declination, surgery) - 1951-1957 Reusse, J.J. - (fellowship, pharmacology) - 1951-1952 Verhoestraete, Louis - (fellowship, maternal and child health) - 1952-1954 Verschaeve, Georgine - (fellowship, nursing) - 1948, 1952-1953
    - DMPH Brazil, 1952-1955 (Box 16, Folder 137)
      Barbosa, Antonio Motto de Souza - (fellowship, pathology) - 1954 Carvalho, Zilda - (nursing) - 1953 De Dio, Americo - (anatomy) - 1955 Ricciardi, Ivan - (entomology) - 1952-1953
    - DMPH Canada, 1949-1958 (Box 16, Folder 138)
      Chevrier, Douglas - (University of Manitoba) - (Office of the Registrar) - 1953 Cote, Raymond - (declination, bacteriological chemistry) - 1953 Fraser, Frank Clarke - (medical genetics) - 1954-1956 Genest, Jacques - (medicine) - 1949-1958 Hoffer, Abram - (travel, psychiatry and public health) - 1954 McDougall, Ruth - (child health) - 1952-1953 McGill University - (psychiatry) - 1953-1955 McLeod, Wendell - (medical education) - 1951-1957 Trapp, Ethlyn - (radiology) - 1950-1954
    - DMPH Ceylon, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 139)
      Amarasinghe, Aryadasa - (veterinary medicine) - 1953 Bibile, Elizabeth Monica - (fellow, nursing) - 1952-1953 Nursing - 1950-1953
    - DMPH Chile, 1953-1955 (Box 16, Folder 140)
      Ayub, Victor - (travel, public health) - 1953-1954 Izquierdo, Luiz - (fellowship, entomology) - 1954-1955
    - DMPH Denmark - Aarhus Schools of Nursing, 1950-1954 (Box 16, Folder 141)
    - DMPH Denmark - Aarhus University - Department of Psychiatry - (Stromgren, Eric), 1948-1958 (Box 16, Folder 142)
    - DMPH Denmark - Aarhus University Hospital, 1947-1957 (Box 17, Folder 143)
    - DMPH Denmark - Backer, Kaj Henning - (travel, public health), 1947-1953 (Box 17, Folder 144)
    - DMPH Denmark - Copenhagen Rigshospitalet - Department of Internal Medicine, 1947-1956 (Box 17, Folder 145)
    - DMPH Denmark - Copenhagen Rigshospitalet - Department of Pediatrics - (Plum, Preben), 1947-1956 (Box 17, Folder 146)
    - DMPH Denmark - Copenhagen Rigshospitalet - Medical Department A, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 147)
    - DMPH Denmark - Copenhagen State Serum Institute - (Orskov, Jeppe), 1945-1956 (Box 17, Folder 148)
    - DMPH Denmark - Copenhagen University - (general), 1951-1953 (Box 17, Folder 149)
    - DMPH Denmark - Copenhagen University - Child Guidance Clinic - (Farup, Bodil), 1948-1956 (Box 17, Folder 150)
    - DMPH Denmark - Copenhagen University - Institute of Human Genetics, 1934-1939, 1948-1958 (Box 17, Folder 151)
    - DMPH Denmark - Copenhagen University - Institute of Hygiene - (Bonnevie, Paul), 1949-1953 (Box 17, Folder 152)
    - DMPH Denmark - Copenhagen University - Library of Technical Hygiene - (Jensen, Karl Eric), 1949-1955 (Box 17, Folder 153)
    - DMPH Denmark, 1948-1954 (Box 17, Folder 154)
      Danish Society for Mental Health - 1948, 1954 Declination(s) - Grut, Aage - (industrial hygiene) - 1953 Engell, Hans Christian - (fellowship, surgery) - 1952-1954 Ethelberg, Sven - (neurosurgery) - 1951-1953 Foget, Maria - (travel, nursing) - 1951-1954 Ginger-Mortensen, Ellen Elise - (fellowship, nursing) - 1951-1954
    - DMPH Denmark, 1950-1954 (Box 18, Folder 155)
      Holm, Johannes Herman - (fellowship, public health) - 1951-1952 Jensen, Reimer J. - (fellowship, psychology) - 1950-1954
    - DMPH Denmark, 1952-1956 (Box 18, Folder 156)
      Jerne, Nils - (declination, biology) - 1952-1954 Larsen, Jytte Funder and Nielsen, Ingrid - (travel, nursing) - 1954-1956
    - DMPH Denmark - Lund, Mogens - (travel neurology), 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 157)
    - DMPH Denmark, 1952-1955 (Box 18, Folder 158)
      Mahrt-Olsen, Elsa - (fellowship, nursing) - 1952-1954 Moller, Karl Herbert - (fellowship, public health) - 1954-1955
    - DMPH Denmark - National Health Service - Department of Statistics - (Frandsen, J., Lindhardt, M.), 1946-1956 (Box 18, Folder 159)
    - DMPH Denmark - National Health Service - Department of Statistics - Documents (11), 1950-1957 (Box 18, Folder 160)
    - DMPH Denmark - Nursing, 1950-1957 (Box 18, Folder 161)
    - DMPH Denmark - Scheibel, Inga - (travel, immunology), 1951-1952 (Box 18, Folder 162)
    - DMPH Denmark, 1951-1953 (Box 18, Folder 163)
      Vermehren, Agnete - (hospital dietetics) - 1953 Vesterdal, Jorgen - (fellowship, pediatrics) - 1951-1952
    - DMPH East Africa - Uganda - Community development, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 164)
    - DMPH Egypt - Egyptian Health Survey, 1952-1953 (Box 19, Folder 165)
    - DMPH England, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 166)
      Ackers, G. Lloyd - (travel, sanitation) - 1953 Acton Technical College - (Harcourt, Robert) - (psychology) - 1953 Allison, Anthony - (hematology) - 1953-1954
    - DMPH England - Birmingham Medical School - Department of Anatomy - (Zuckerman, S.), 1947-1956 (Box 19, Folder 167)
    - DMPH England - Birmingham Medical School - Department of Experimental Psychiatry - (Elkes, J.), 1952-1958 (Box 19, Folder 168)
    - DMPH England - Birmingham Medical School - Department of Medical Statistics - (Hogber, Lancelot), 1947-1955 (Box 19, Folder 169)
    - DMPH England - Birmingham Medical School - Department of Social Medicine - (McKeown, Thomas), 1946-1956 (Box 19, Folder 170)
    - DMPH England - Birmingham Regional Hospital Board, 1952-1953 (Box 19, Folder 171)
      Blaschko, H. - (Oxford University) - (Department of Pharmacology) - 1952-1953 Bonnin, Josiah Grant - (Orthopaedic Surgery) - 1953
    - DMPH England, 1947-1958 (Box 19, Folder 172)
      Bristol University - (Medical School) - (visits) - 1951-1957 British Occupational Hygiene Society - 1952-1954 British Postgraduate Medical School - 1947-1958 Brackington, Colin Fraser - (travel, social medicine) - 1950-1954
    - DMPH England - Burden Neurological Clinic, 1939, 1946-1955 (Box 19, Folder 173)
    - DMPH England - Burden Neurological Clinic - Supplementary material, 1939-1951; 11 items (Box 19, Folder 174)
    - DMPH England - Cambridge University - Department of Engineering, 1950-1954 (Box 20, Folder 175)
    - DMPH England - Cambridge University - Department of Human Ecology, 1951-1957 (Box 20, Folder 176)
    - DMPH England - Cambridge University - Department of Pathology, 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 177)
    - DMPH England - Cambridge University - Physiological Laboratory, 1946-1955 (Box 20, Folder 178)
    - DMPH England - Cambridge University - Psychological Laboratory, 1936-1938, 1947-1955 (Box 20, Folder 179)
    - DMPH England, 1949-1954 (Box 20, Folder 180)
      Calma, I. - (neurophysiology) - 1953 Chadwick Lectures - (sanitation) - (Burden, Robert P. and Logan, John A.) - 1953-1954 Chesterman, Clement C. - (public health) - 1952-1954 Colonial Insecticides Committee - 1951-1952 Colonial Office - 1949-1955
    - DMPH England, 1952-1959 (Box 20, Folder 181)
      Cornist, R.J. - (travel, public health engineering) - 1952-1959 Cosh, J.A. - (medical education) - 1953
    - DMPH England - Coxon, Robert Victor - (human physiology), 1951-1953 (Box 20, Folder 182)
    - DMPH England - Cruickshank, Robert - (preventive medicine), 1948-1954 (Box 20, Folder 183)
    - DMPH England, 1951-1955 (Box 21, Folder 184)
      Davies, C.N. - (travel, physics) - 1953-1954 Declination - Royal College of Surgeons - Department of Pharmacology - 1955 Declination - Sayer, Jasper - (request for diagnosis) - 1955 Declination - Sessions Hodge, R. - (neuropsychiatry) - 1954 Pitchburn, P.W. - (physics) - 1952 Dixon, Hylda - (nursing) - 1952-1954 Downman, Charles B.B. - (travel, neurophysiology) - 1951-1953 Drego, Montagu J. - (neuropsychiatry) - 1952
    - DMPH England - Durham University, 1950-1957 (Box 21, Folder 185)
      Department of Civil Engineering - 1950-1957 Department of Educational Psychology - 1951-1952
    - DMPH England, 1947-1954 (Box 21, Folder 186)
      Eysenck, Hans Jurgen - (travel, psychiatry) - 1947-1954 Floyd, William Frederich - (travel, psychology) - 1953
    - DMPH England - Galton Laboratory - (human genetics), 1935-1936. 1946-1954 (Box 21, Folder 187)
    - DMPH England, 1950-1954 (Box 21, Folder 188)
      Goldberg, Elsa Mathilde - (travel, psychiatric social work) - 1950-1953 Goodwin, John F. - (travel, medicine, cardiovascular research) - 1952-1954 Gregory, Roderick Alfred - (travel, phsyiology) - 1953 Harvey, Brian Hugh - (fellowship, industrial hygiene) - 1952-1954
    - DMPH England, 1946-1955 (Box 21, Folder 189)
      Heady, James Austin - (travel, statistics) - 1946, 1952-1953 Herford, Martin - (industrial hygiene) - 1954-1955 Katz, Bernhard - (travel, neurophysiology) - 1950-1955 King Edward's Hospital Fund - 1953-1955
    - DMPH England - Lawson, Mabel Gordon - (travel, nursing), 1949-1953 (Box 21, Folder 190)
    - DMPH England, 1941-1955 (Box 21, Folder 191)
      Leeds University - (Faculty of Medicine) - 1948-1955 Liverpool University - School of Tropical Medicine - 1941-1954
    - DMPH England - London Hospital Medical College, 1951-1954 (Box 22, Folder 192)
    - DMPH England - London Institute of Civil Engineers, 1950-1953 (Box 22, Folder 193)
    - DMPH England - London Institute of Civil Engineers, 1954-1958 (Box 22, Folder 194)
    - DMPH England - London Institute of Civil Engineers - Documents (28) - 1952-1958, 1950-1958 (Box 22, Folder 195)
    - DMPH England - London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine, 1952-1955 (Box 22, Folder 196)
    - DMPH England - London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - Department of Occupational Health, 1953-1958 (Box 22, Folder 197)
    - DMPH England - London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - Environmental Sanitation, 1953-1955 (Box 22, Folder 198)
    - DMPH England - London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - Watford Experimental Health Unit, 1950-1956 (Box 22, Folder 199)
    - DMPH England - London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine - Watford Experimental Health Unit, 1950-1956 (Box 22, Folder 200)
    - DMPH England - Mackintosh, J.M. - (Sanitary engineering), 1941-1942, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 201)
    - DMPH England - Manchester University, 1947-1953 (Box 23, Folder 202)
    - DMPH England - Manchester University - Department of Medicine, 1952-1954 (Box 23, Folder 203)
    - DMPH England - Manchester University - Health Center - Documents (14) - 1951-1958, 1950-1958 (Box 23, Folder 204)
    - DMPH England - Manchester University - Health Center - Documents (14) - 1951-1958, 1950-1958 (Box 23, Folder 205)
    - DMPH England - Maudsley Hospital - Institute of Psychiatry, 1947-1956 (Box 23, Folder 206)
    - DMPH England - Medical Research Council - Equipment, 1949-1953 (Box 23, Folder 207)
    - DMPH England - Medical Research Council - General Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 23, Folder 208)
    - DMPH England - Medical Research Council - Fellowships, 1951-1957 (Box 23, Folder 209)
    - DMPH England - Medical Research Council - Fellowships, 1951-1957 (Box 23, Folder 210)
    - DMPH England - Medical Research Council - Fellowships, 1951-1957 (Box 23, Folder 211)
    - DMPH England, 1948-1958 (Box 24, Folder 212)
      MacMahon, Brian - (fellowship, social medicine) - 1952-1953 Mental Health Research Fund - 1952-1958 Ministry of Health - (Charles, John A.) - (travel) - 1948-1955 Moss, Louis - (social science) - 1955
    - DMPH England, 1943-1955 (Box 24, Folder 213)
      Murray, Robert - (travel, industrial hygiene) - 1952-1954 National Foundation for Educational Research - 1952-1954 National Institute for Medical Research - 1943-1955
    - DMPH England - National Hospital Queen Square - (nervous diseases), 1939, 1947-1957 (Box 24, Folder 214)
    - DMPH England - Nuffield Foundation, 1942-1954 (Box 24, Folder 215)
    - DMPH England - Nursing, 1951-1955 (Box 24, Folder 216)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University, 1944-1955 (Box 24, Folder 217)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - Department of Pharmacology, 1938, 1949-1953 (Box 24, Folder 218)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - First International Neurological Symposium, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 219)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - Institute of Experimental Psychology, 1952-1957 (Box 24, Folder 220)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - Institute of Human Anatomy, 1949-1958 (Box 24, Folder 221)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - Institute of Human Anatomy - Reprints (12), 1947-1955 (Box 24, Folder 222)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - Institute of Physiology, 1929-1935, 1949-1957 (Box 25, Folder 223)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - Laboratory of Human Nutrition, 1947-1957 (Box 25, Folder 224)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - Radcliffe Infirmary, 1941-1954 (Box 25, Folder 225)
      (centrifuge) - 1941-1947 (Coombs, Patricia) - 1941-1954
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - Radcliffe Infirmary, 1941-1954 (Box 25, Folder 226)
    - DMPH England - Oxford University - Radcliffe Medical School, 1954-1957 (Box 25, Folder 227)
    - DMPH England - Rickham, Peter Paul - (travel, pediatric surgery), 1950-1952 (Box 25, Folder 228)
    - DMPH England - Pemberton, John - (travel, social medicine), 1950-1954 (Box 25, Folder 229)
    - DMPH England - Roffey Park Rehabilitation Center, 1947-1953 (Box 25, Folder 230)
    - DMPH England - Roth, Martin - (neuropsychiatry), 1951-1954 (Box 25, Folder 231)
    - DMPH England - Royal Anthropological Institute - Blood Group, 1951-1955 (Box 25, Folder 232)
    - DMPH England - Royal College of Nursing, 1946-1953 (Box 25, Folder 233)
    - DMPH England - Royal National Throat, Nose, and Ear Hospital, 1948-1954 (Box 25, Folder 234)
    - DMPH England - Royal Sanitary Institute, 1951-1954 (Box 25, Folder 235)
      Margate Congress - 1951-1952 Hastings Congress - 1952-1953 Scarborough Congress - 1953-1954
    - DMPH England - Royal Society of Medicine, 1949-1954 (Box 25, Folder 236)
    - DMPH England - Royal Victoria Infirmary - Child Health Department, 1947-1955 (Box 25, Folder 237)
    - DMPH England - Royal Victoria Infirmary and King's College Medical School - Department of Psychological Medicine, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 238)
    - DMPH England - St. Bartholemew's Hospital - Department of Pathology, 1953-1956 (Box 26, Folder 239)
    - DMPH England - St. George's Hospital School of Nursing, 1953-1955 (Box 26, Folder 240)
    - DMPH England - St. Mary's Hospital Medical School, 1943-1944, 1952-1955 (Box 26, Folder 241)